Guide to the Edith Wharton Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Oversize, 1900-80; 2; (1 box)
  - Photographs: Wharton, Edith [three prints, one by Zaida Ben Yusuf], ca. 1900 (Folder 1839 (broadside)–1841 (broadside))
  - Photograph: Austin, Mary [Great great grandmother] (Folder 1842 (broadside))
  - Photograph: Sargent, John Singer, charcoal sketch of Henry James, 1912 (Folder 1843 (broadside))
  - Photograph: Stevens, Ebenezer [Great grandfather] (Folder 1844 (broadside))
  - Photograph: Stevens, Mrs. [Great grandmother] (Folder 1845 (broadside))
  - Photograph: Wharton, Edward, ca. 1900 (Folder 1846 (broadside))
  - Photograph: Homes, "The Mount," Grounds and Gardens [East Garden] (Folder 1847 (broadside))
  - Commemorative stamp plate blocks, 1980 (Folder 1848 (broadside))
  - Commemorative stamp poster, 1980 (Folder 1849 (Art))
  - La Farge, John. "Sifa Dancing the Sitting Siva" (Illustration for La Farge's Reminiscences of the South Seas, photographic reproduction of drawing) Gift of Gaillard Lapsley, n.d. (Folder 1850 (Art))
  - Maarek, ---. Portrait of Walter van Rensselaer Berry (oil on canvas, 22.25" x 22"), n.d. (Folder 1851 (Art))
  - "My Work Among the Women Workers of Paris" (newspaper article) (Series V), 1915 Nov 28 (Folder 1852 (Art))